

Personal Info

Jalan Gombak, Kuala Lumpur, 53100, Malaysia 01123270509

2911safi@gmail.com

Links

Article website
Setia Awan
Admin Site
Sports Information

Skills

JavaScript

CSS

HTML

MySQL

NodeJs

Angular

MongoDB

Git

Responsive Design

Teamwork

Problem-solving

Languages

Pashto

English

Qandagha Safi

Web Developer

Summary

As a team-oriented and skilled Computer Science graduate with over 4 years of progressive experience in software engineering and web development, I am eager to seek a challenging position in your esteemed organization. As an Afghan national who has studied and worked in Malaysia, I am available to start working immediately.

Work Experience

Web developer, MYCN Sdn Bhd, Kuala Lumpur

June 2019 - Present

I have been working on a large and complex project. My key responsibilities and achievements include:

- Writing reusable and clean programing code to develop 12/18 web and backend services.
- Working on frontend and backend using Nodejs, Angular, Mongodb, Redis, Zookeeper

Software engineer and web developer, Tektician (Part-Time), Perak January 2019 - June 2019

My main responsibilities and achievements include:

- Enhancing customizing ERPnext components
- Writing clean frontend and backend code for features.

Education

Bacheloar's OF Computer Science, IIUM (3.65)

August 2014 - February 2019

Courses

Become a Full-Stack Web Developer, LinkedIn

January 2023 - February 2023

Career Essentials in Software Development by Microsoft and LinkedIn, Microsoft

January 2023 - February 2023

References

jonathan@tektician.com

hgun77@gmail.com